María Florencia Pereira

Personal Information

Full name: María Florencia PereiraBirth date: December 2nd, 1987

Residence: ArgentinaNationality: ArgentinianCivil Status: single

• Email: mflorenciapereira@gmail.com

• Website: http://mflorenciapereira-mflorp.rhcloud.com



Goal

Develop a professional career in the area of information systems, at a company where I can contribute with my analytic and technical skills. Gain work experience by taking part in projects where I can apply my knowledge of software development, system security, programming languages and system deployment.

Academic Background

2006 - 2012

<u>Bachelor's Degree</u> *Instituto F.A.S.T.A San Vicente de Paul*

2006 - 2012

Information Systems Engineer
Faculty of Engineering
Buenos Aires University
Av. Paseo Colón 850, Capital Federal, Argentina
Career Average: 8.07 / 10

2016 - Present

<u>Master in Information Security</u>
Faculty of Engineering, Exact Sciences and Economic Sciences
Buenos Aires University

Skillset

- <u>Programming languages:</u> JAVA,C,C++, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, Shell scripting, Perl.
- Frontend: HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS, SASS, XSLT, XPATH, i18n.
- <u>JAVA Frameworks:</u> Android, Angular JS, Node JS, Express J S, JQuery, Ajax, Wicket, Struts, Tiles, Ext JS, Spring, Quartz, JBPM.
- PHP Framworks: Codeigniter, Laravel.

- Rails Frameworks: Rails, Device.
- Report generation: Jasper Reports, Crystal Reports.
- <u>Servers:</u> Weblogic, Tomcat.
- <u>Testing:</u> JUnit, Mockito, RSpec.
- Databases; SQL, MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB, Mongoose, Hibernate, JPA.
- <u>Tools:</u> Jenkins, Maven, Sonar Qube, Eclipse, IntelliJ IDEA, GIT, SVN, Mercurial, Enterprise Architect.
- System analysis and management: UML, Crisp-DM, PMBOK.

Languages

English

1994-2008

English course

Advanced oral and written English.

Academia Cultural Inglesa de Devoto

Av. Lincoln 4255, Capital Federal, Argentina

French

2013 - 2014

Elementary French Course
Basic oral and written French.
Alliance Francaise
Av. Córdoba 936, Capital Federal, Argentina

Certificates

2008

<u>Certificate of Proficiency in English (CPE)</u> C2 Level Cambridge University

2007

Certificate in Advanced English (CAE)
C1 Level
Cambridge University

2005

First Certificate in English (FCE)
B2 Level
Cambridge University

Work experience

08/2011 - 04/2012 <u>DCC Soft</u>

JAVA Developer

Web development using JAVA, Struts, Struts Taglibs, Hibernate, Tomcat, Ext JS, Quartz, JSON, Jasper Reports, JBPM, Tiles, JSP, MySQL.

05/2012 - PRESENT

Fundación de Hemofilia

JAVA EE Developer

Freelance, voluntary job. Final project for Information Systems Engineering. Web development using JAVA, Spring, Hibernate, Tomcat, JSP, JQuery, JSON, Jasper Reports, MySQL. The job involves requirement capture, analysis, design, implementation, deployment and training.

02/2013 - PRESENT

Ternium (Snoop Consulting)

JAVA Developer

JAVA development using the company's platform, Maven, Spring, XStream, Web Services, Oracle, Crystal Reports, Quartz, JPA and Weblogic.